<files><attributes><name>Impact of Electron-Electron Cusp on Configuration Interaction Energies</name><abstract>The effect of the electron-electron cusp on the convergence of configuration
  interaction (CI) wave functions is examined. By analogy with the
  pseudopotential approach for electron-ion interactions, an effective
  electron-electron interaction is developed which closely reproduces the
  scattering of the Coulomb interaction but is smooth and finite at zero
  electron-electron separation. The exact many-electron wave function for this
  smooth effective interaction has no cusp at zero electron-electron separation.
  We perform CI and quantum Monte Carlo calculations for He and Be atoms, both
  with the Coulomb electron-electron interaction and with the smooth effective
  electron-electron interaction. We find that convergence of the CI expansion of
  the wave function for the smooth electron-electron interaction is not
  significantly improved compared with that for the divergent Coulomb interaction
  for energy differences on the order of 1 mHartree. This shows that, contrary to
  popular belief, description of the electron-electron cusp is not a limiting
  factor, to within chemical accuracy, for CI calculations.</abstract><data>http://arxiv.org/pdf/cond-mat/0102536v1</data><id>0</id></attributes><attributes><name>KnightCap: A chess program that learns by combining TD(lambda) with
  game-tree search</name><abstract>In this paper we present TDLeaf(lambda), a variation on the TD(lambda)
  algorithm that enables it to be used in conjunction with game-tree search. We
  present some experiments in which our chess program ``KnightCap'' used
  TDLeaf(lambda) to learn its evaluation function while playing on the Free
  Internet Chess Server (FICS, fics.onenet.net). The main success we report is
  that KnightCap improved from a 1650 rating to a 2150 rating in just 308 games
  and 3 days of play. As a reference, a rating of 1650 corresponds to about level
  B human play (on a scale from E (1000) to A (1800)), while 2150 is human master
  level. We discuss some of the reasons for this success, principle among them
  being the use of on-line, rather than self-play.</abstract><data>http://arxiv.org/pdf/cs/9901002v1</data><id>1</id></attributes><attributes><name>Local Light Field Fusion: Practical View Synthesis with Prescriptive
  Sampling Guidelines</name><abstract>We present a practical and robust deep learning solution for capturing and
  rendering novel views of complex real world scenes for virtual exploration.
  Previous approaches either require intractably dense view sampling or provide
  little to no guidance for how users should sample views of a scene to reliably
  render high-quality novel views. Instead, we propose an algorithm for view
  synthesis from an irregular grid of sampled views that first expands each
  sampled view into a local light field via a multiplane image (MPI) scene
  representation, then renders novel views by blending adjacent local light
  fields. We extend traditional plenoptic sampling theory to derive a bound that
  specifies precisely how densely users should sample views of a given scene when
  using our algorithm. In practice, we apply this bound to capture and render
  views of real world scenes that achieve the perceptual quality of Nyquist rate
  view sampling while using up to 4000x fewer views. We demonstrate our
  approach's practicality with an augmented reality smartphone app that guides
  users to capture input images of a scene and viewers that enable realtime
  virtual exploration on desktop and mobile platforms.</abstract><data>http://arxiv.org/pdf/1905.00889v1</data><id>2</id></attributes></files>